<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on David Sedley</title>
    <link>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on David Sedley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rara avis (infrequent flyer)</title>
      <link>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/flying/</guid>
      <description>I would love to hear (dns1@cam.ac.uk) from any other academics who have substantially reduced their flying or are keen to do so, and from anyone with information on practical alternatives to academic travel, e.g. high-quality video-conferencing.
From interview in Times Higher Education, 18 June 2009 (link to full article)
FORGET THE PLANE, TAKE THE TRAIN: EVERYONE CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE
For David Sedley, Laurence professor of ancient philosophy at the University of Cambridge, academics have been too slow to acknowledge how their actions contribute to climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video and audio</title>
      <link>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/audio_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/audio_video/</guid>
      <description> Audio In Our Time (with Melvyn Bragg, BBC Radio 4):  Stoicism, March 2005 Socrates, September 2007 Epicureanism, February 2013  Other:  Socrates vs Darwin, May 2009, Lady Margaret Lecture, Christ’s College Podcast interview on Stoicism with Peter Adamson, January 2012  Video  Ancient atheism, interview with Tim Whitmarsh, August 2013 Godlikeness, valedictory lecture, May 2014 Plato&amp;rsquo;s theory of Forms, Royal Institute of Philosophy lecture, December 2014  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work in progress</title>
      <link>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/work_in_progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://DavidSedley.github.io/other/work_in_progress/</guid>
      <description>Articles and conference/seminar papers ‘Divine anonymity’ ‘Theological dualism and the origins of Greek philosophy’ ‘Why aren&amp;rsquo;t atoms coloured?’ ‘Lucretius on imagination and mental projection’ ‘Etymology in Plato’s Sophist&amp;lsquo; ‘Are Platonic Forms concepts?’ ‘Academic Legacies&amp;rsquo; (for Oxford Handbook of Hellenistic Philosophy) Books Themes in Greek theology based on 2014 lectures at Renmin University, Beijing, currently being translated for publication in Chinese; English version to follow later.
Plato’s Phaedo not a commentary but a discursive study of the whole dialogue</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>